hi spring fans welcome to another
嗨，春季粉丝们欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips in this
在此安装弹簧提示
installment we're going to look at how
分期付款，我们将研究如何
to create a web socket based API using
使用创建基于Web套接字的API
the new reactive spring web flex API and
新的反应式Spring Web Flex API和
Spring Framework 5 when we looked when
当我们看Spring Framework 5的时候
we last looked at service and events we
我们最后看了我们的服务和事件
saw that building a server-side push
看到建立服务器端推送
mechanism using service and events and
使用服务和事件的机制，以及
the spring web flex api was cognitively
Spring Web Flex API是认知上的
very simple and we didn't have to do a
非常简单，我们不必做
lot of gymnastics mental or otherwise to
精神上或其他方面的很多体操
make this work and we'll find that the
使这项工作，我们会发现
same is true today when we build our web
今天，当我们建立网站时也是如此
socket API now before we can build the
现在我们可以建立套接字API
actual API itself we need a client right
实际的API本身，我们需要客户权限
so we're gonna build a trivial client
所以我们要建立一个琐碎的客户
today using angular for and angular for
今天使用angular for和angular for
you features a language called
您使用一种称为
typescript so we can say ng new wshh
打字稿，所以我们可以说ng new wshh
client and this will take actually about
客户，这实际上需要大约
a minute for this process to a to abate
一分钟的时间来减轻
now we have a new client I'm going to
现在我们有一个新客户
open this offender ID as I was saying
就像我说的那样打开这个罪犯的身份证
this this project is using angular for
这个项目正在使用角度
which in turn uses typescript now we've
依次使用打字稿，我们现在
chosen to use angular and typescript
选择使用角度和打字稿
because it's a very familiar environment
因为这是一个非常熟悉的环境
a very familiar language of ever if
有史以来很熟悉的语言
you've ever built anything using Cottman
您曾经使用Cottman构建任何东西
which will do for the server-side right
这将为服务器端的权利
this is a nice excuse since we're
这是一个很好的借口，因为我们
already using a foreign language to both
已经都使用外语了
this client to also build a service
这个客户也要建立服务
implementation using the continent
使用大陆实施
programming language which of course
编程语言
spring boot readily in natively supports
spring boot 很容易在本地支持
so we have our new application and we're
所以我们有了新的应用程序，
gonna build the application you know
将构建您知道的应用程序
we're just gonna build a very simple
我们只是要建立一个非常简单的
component here we're gonna go to the
组件在这里，我们要去
root component called AB component and
根组件称为AB组件，
we're going to build a simple template
我们将建立一个简单的模板
in line we're not gonna specify a you
顺便说一句，我们不会指定您
know separate one just to keep things
知道一个人只是为了保留东西
simple
简单
protip I learned this one from a tree
我从树上学到了这个
people don't let this generate
人们不要让它产生
JavaScript for you so I'm gonna say h1
您的JavaScript，所以我要说H1
files and the idea is we're gonna have a
文件，想法是我们要有一个
a service that lists any new files that
列出任何新文件的服务
appear in a directory right not a very
出现在目录中不是很好
interesting example but it does that it
有趣的例子，但确实如此
does allow us to sort of demonstrate a
确实使我们能够演示
few different concepts as we use the the
我们使用几个不同的概念
website API and the reactive sort of
网站API和反应式
plumbing in the background now we're
在后台水暖我们
gonna have a listing of files but for
会有文件清单，但是
now you know this just get the simplest
现在你知道这只是最简单的
machinery week that we can working so
机械周，我们可以这样工作
that we can sort of stub it out later
我们可以稍后再存根
and then see if it works so let's say
然后看看它是否有效，让我们说
we're gonna have a collection of div
我们将有一个div的集合
elements one for each item in a list of
元素列表中的每一项
file events right so let's say that
文件事件正确，所以我们说
there's a new file in and they get sent
里面有一个新文件，他们被发送了
down by WebSockets to the client the
通过WebSockets到客户端
which then uses those that updated
然后使用更新的
information to update a collection
更新集合的信息
that's keeping on the client here ok so
这样可以让客户满意
I want to say let f of files and we'll
我想说让文件f，我们将
write out the information about the file
写出有关文件的信息
so we're gonna I'd out write out the the
所以我们要写出
path and maybe the session ID so we'll
路径以及会话ID，因此我们将
say span style font size is equal to
说跨度样式字体大小等于
smaller
较小的
and then we'll write out the session ID
然后我们写出会话ID
so the session ID very good so now we've
因此会话ID非常好，现在我们已经
got that now we needed of course to to
现在我们当然需要
actually define the type so when you
实际定义类型，以便当您
define an interface file event like so
像这样定义一个接口文件事件
I'm gonna give it a path string a
我要给它一个路径字符串
session ID string and we'll write that
会话ID字符串，我们将其写为
out and now we'll create a field to
现在，我们将创建一个字段
manage our array our array of file at in
管理我们的数组，我们的文件数组位于
strand so file event equals an empty
使文件事件等于空
array list an empty array now we need a
数组列出一个空数组，现在我们需要一个
constructor naturally and then in the
构造函数，然后在
constructor we're going to use a
构造函数，我们将使用
WebSocket client so I'm gonna say new
WebSocket客户端，所以我要说新的
web socket and in this case we'll use
网络套接字，在这种情况下，我们将使用
the WS prefix of course 8080 that's what
当然是8080的WS前缀
our service is running and we need an
我们的服务正在运行，我们需要一个
endpoint name so the input name could be
端点名称，因此输入名称可以是
anything really I'm gonna just call it
任何我真正要称呼的东西
WS files and we'll use that here in the
WS文件，我们将在此处使用
client codes I'm gonna say this dot on
客户代码，我要说这个点
message equals I'm gonna give it a
信息等于我要给它一个
callback and the callback is gonna be
回调，回调将是
it's gonna contain a message a parameter
它会包含一条消息，参数
here of type message event so message
这里是消息事件类型，所以消息
event equals and then we're gonna
事件等于然后我们要
provide a lambda here it's to a callback
在这里提供一个lambda到回调
invocation and what's gonna happen is
调用，将要发生的是
when we get that new message event when
当我们收到新消息事件时
a dereference the data I'm going to
取消引用我要去的数据
store that in a variable here we're
将其存储在一个变量中
gonna store it as a Const actually since
实际上，因为它会存储为Const
we're not gonna change it ever and we're
我们永远都不会改变它，而我们
gonna parse it all right it's gonna come
会解析它会来的
in as a string we expect and we can then
我们期望以字符串形式输入，然后我们可以
take that parse thing and cast it to a
把那个解析的东西放到一个
file a tin so actually the data is is a
归档文件，因此实际上数据是
file of it try and we know that because
它的文件尝试，我们知道，因为
it's a it's been you know design that
这是你知道设计
way but we don't need this extra we'd
方式，但我们不需要这多余的东西
done in declaration right it does type
在声明中完成它确实输入
inference very nicely so finally we're
推论很好，最后我们
gonna write this data to the files
要将这些数据写入文件
collection and you know our template
收藏，你知道我们的模板
well because of the two-way binding in
很好，因为双向绑定
place thanks to angular it'll update
地方感谢角度它将更新
with the new data so that's about it
与新数据有关
that's all we need for our client
这就是我们为客户所需要的
experience to get everything working so
使一切正常运行的经验
let's go ahead and start with that
让我们开始吧
application running here and the same
在这里运行的应用程序相同
node ng serve open
打开节点
it's gonna start up a browser running
它将启动运行的浏览器
the application import 4200 the first
该应用程序首先导入4200
time it loads it's a little slow but you
它加载的时间有点慢，但是你
know we can see it's working it's tried
知道我们可以看到它正在工作
to connect you can see if you look at
连接，您可以看看是否
the console here and the network
这里的控制台和网络
activity it's tried to connect the
活动尝试连接
localhost 8080 WS files of course but
本地主机8080 WS文件，但是
nothing happened we need to provide a
什么都没发生，我们需要提供
working service so let's do that we're
工作服务，让我们做到这一点
gonna go to start that spring at i/o I'm
我要去那个春天开始
gonna go to the cotton you know the copy
要去棉花你知道副本
I'm gonna choose Kotlin as my language
我要选择Kotlin作为我的语言
here and we're gonna use spring boot to
在这里，我们将使用 spring boot
dot om3 so this is the latest and
点om3，所以这是最新的
greatest spring boot as of this revision
截至本修订版的最佳 spring boot
as of this time which allows us to build
截至目前，这使我们能够建立
a you know reactive application using
你知道反应式应用程序使用
spring frame of 5 and the reactive
弹簧架5和无功
support therein so I'm gonna use the
支持其中，所以我要使用
reactive web and of course we're gonna
反应性网络，我们当然要
use spring integration we'll come back
使用spring集成，我们会回来的
to what we're doing with that a little
到我们正在做的一点
bit but for now we have everything we
有点，但是现在我们拥有了一切
need so let's go to the console here up
需要，让我们转到这里的控制台
one level unzip WS service CD WS service
一级解压缩WS服务CD WS服务
and let's open this up alright now we've
现在我们打开它
got a new project so the first aim shall
有了一个新项目，所以第一个目标应该是
be to just to define a skeletal web saw
只是为了定义一个骨骼锯
web socket sort of service something it
Web套接字的某种服务
sends down basic data doesn't have to be
发送基本数据并不一定要
particularly interesting we just want to
特别有趣，我们只想
prove that the plumbing is working and
证明该管道正在工作，并且
so we'll do that first WS service
所以我们将首先进行WS服务
application and let's get some
应用程序，让我们得到一些
configuration so I'm gonna have a a web
配置，所以我要一个网站
socket configuration class and the
套接字配置类和
configuration class defines three things
配置类定义了三件事
of interest first it defines a web
首先要定义一个网络
socket Handler and a web socket handler
套接字处理程序和Web套接字处理程序
is a component that responds to requests
是响应请求的组件
so I say return web socket handler
所以我说返回Web套接字处理程序
okay and of course we'll get a session
好的，我们当然会
and their contract here is that we have
他们在这里的合同是
to return data eventually have to return
返回数据最终不得不返回
a and empty we have to return the the
一个空的我们必须返回
the return value of calling session dot
呼叫会话点的返回值
send or something like that right mono
发送或类似的权利单声道
the empty will probably work right so
空可能会正确工作，所以
let's try that return this does that
让我们尝试返回此操作
work
工作
no empty looks let's see this monitor
没有空的外观让我们看一下这款显示器
with WebSocket Handler is expecting a
与WebSocket处理程序期望
mono void so we can just return that
单声道无效，所以我们可以返回
mono dot d all right flux MD
单点d通量MD
yes we can return null for now well it
是的，我们现在可以返回null
doesn't matter what we'll have to come
不管我们要做什么
back to this anyway so let's leave that
还是回到这个，让我们离开那个
for now okay to do and then we need a
现在可以做，然后我们需要一个
WebSocket Handler adapter goes web
WebSocket处理程序适配器进入网络
socket and ER adapter very good that
插座和ER适配器非常好
one's pretty straightforward and then we
一个人很简单，然后我们
need a handler mapping right so fun and
需要一个有趣的处理程序映射，并且
their mapping equals handler mapping and
它们的映射等于处理程序映射，
the handler mapping is a object that's
处理程序映射是一个
designed to tell spring the web runtime
旨在告诉Spring Web运行时
what what components are mounted to
什么组件安装到
which end points right so simple URL and
哪个端点指向如此简单的网址，
their mapping and importantly we need
他们的映射，重要的是我们需要
this to you know have a certain order
你知道这有一定顺序
let's just say ten it has to be
我们只说十个
something non zero here and we need to
这里的东西非零，我们需要
give it then a collection of URLs and
然后给它一个URL的集合，
here we're just going to use a map so a
在这里，我们将使用地图，以便
map of we need one of these convenient
我们需要这些便捷的地图之一
builder API is in common I'm gonna say
我要说的是Builder API的共同点
that the in point WS files should map to
入站WS文件应映射到
WS H which is our component there and
WS H是我们在那里的组成部分，
then we return this definition legs like
然后我们返回这个定义腿像
that okay so there's our handler mapping
好的，所以有我们的处理程序映射
our web socket handler adapter and then
我们的网络套接字处理程序适配器，然后
finally our web socket handler now the
终于我们的网络套接字处理程序了
simplest thing that we can do here is
我们在这里可以做的最简单的事情是
just to return data using the session
只是为了使用会话返回数据
method so the session we you know if we
方法，因此会话我们知道，如果我们
sent session send and pass in a
已发送的会话发送并传递
publisher of WebSocket messages that
WebSocket消息的发布者
would satisfy the contract so let's do
会满足合同，所以我们做
that
那
valve publisher equals flux touch
阀门发行商等于通量接触
generate and we're just gonna generate
产生，我们将产生
some data here because I'm gonna have
这里有一些数据，因为我要
something to work with so we'll generate
可以合作的东西，我们将产生
some data using a consumer of
一些数据使用
synchronous
同步
sink of type file event okay and of
类型文件事件接收器正常且
course we don't have that type file
当然我们没有那个类型文件
event so that's created here from
事件，是从这里创建的
purposes to match the structure that we
目的是要匹配我们的结构
have on a client not that we need it but
客户不是我们需要它，而是
it's just convenient for our purposes
就我们的目的而言很方便
for this demo to have similar objects
为了使该演示具有相似的对象
okay so I'm gonna use a data class and
好吧，我要使用数据类
in Kotlin this makes short work of
在科特林，这使得
generating Gator setters to string all
生成Gator setter以将所有字符串
that kind of stuff so we can now use
这种东西，所以我们现在可以使用
that and we have to return some data
那我们必须返回一些数据
right so we have a set we have a sink
对，所以我们有一个盆，我们有一个水槽
that gets created for us and our job is
为我们创造的，我们的工作是
to return the sink and then put all that
返回水槽，然后放所有
you know to generate data into that sink
您知道将数据生成到该接收器中
so when I generate a new record of type
所以当我产生一个新的记录类型
file event like this and we're just
像这样的文件事件，我们只是
going to hard-code the data so session 1
要对数据进行硬编码，因此会话1
2 3 or even better we can just system
2 3甚至更好，我们可以系统
that current time miller and the path
当前的时间磨工和路径
will be a b c alright so there where
会好起来的abc，所以在那里
there's our custom generator and we can
有我们的自定义生成器，我们可以
return we can say that we want that that
返回我们可以说我们想要那个
publisher to then map its output which
发布商然后映射其输出
is the file event into a string right
是将文件事件转换为字符串吗？
because we need a string so let's use
因为我们需要一个字符串，所以让我们使用
the jackson object mapper so we'll save
杰克逊对象映射器，所以我们将保存
it jackson object mapper i will say i
它是杰克逊对象映射器，我会说我
want to map it to a string now it is an
想要将其映射到字符串，因为它是一个
implicit parameter in a lambda if you
Lambda中的隐式参数（如果您
have a single unambiguous unambiguous
有一个明确的
parameter and a lambda callback method
参数和lambda回调方法
you know the functional interface then
你知道功能接口
Kotlin gives it the implicit name it or
Kotlin为其赋予了隐式名称，或者
you can of course give it a parameter
你当然可以给它一个参数
name like this in which case it no
像这样的名字
longer works but it is what i have here
更长的作品，但这就是我在这里
so that's fine and then we need to map
这样很好，然后我们需要映射
that into a text message as we did
像我们一样将其转换为短信
before taking an int as well and we can
在取得整数之前，我们可以
put that publisher here and return it
把那个出版商放回去
right so yeah we are
对，是的，我们是
now will you have
现在你有
ah I forgot to specify a return value
啊我忘了指定返回值
very good so now we have a return value
很好，所以现在我们有一个返回值
there and we everything else should work
在那里，我们其他一切都应该工作
as we expect it to right so we have now
正如我们期望的那样，所以现在
this basic WebSocket handler nothing
这个基本的WebSocket处理程序没什么
particularly interesting it just you
特别有趣的是你
know it demonstrates how to generate
知道它演示了如何生成
some data the only problem is of course
一些数据当然唯一的问题是
is that if we let this run as is you
是如果我们让它像您一样运行
know scream it'll go just as fast as it
知道尖叫会和它一样快
can not stopping and our browser will
无法停止，我们的浏览器会
very quickly run into memory so let's
很快就会进入内存，所以让我们
get it to let's say one second right
让我们说一秒钟吧
we're gonna insert an artificial delay
我们要插入人为的延迟
but just meaning that we can do because
但只是意味着我们可以做，因为
we have a scheduler in the background
我们在后台有一个调度程序
here right the reactor project which
这里是反应堆项目
underpins the reactive support in spring
支撑春季的反应性支撑
5 gives us a scheduler so let's go ahead
5给了我们一个调度程序，让我们继续吧
and spin this application up and let's
旋转这个应用程序，让我们
not forget next time I'm going to make
下次我会忘记
sure that this instance is this
确保这个实例是这个
application is a single instance only so
应用程序只是一个实例，因此
that way it'll kill the instance there
这样它将杀死那里的实例
and we'll refresh the browser here and
我们将在此处刷新浏览器，然后
there we go every second we get a new
在那里，我们每一秒钟都得到一个新的
result now we could stop here but I want
结果现在我们可以在这里停止，但我想要
to connect our web socket API to things
将我们的Web套接字API连接到事物
that are happening in the world right so
世界上正在发生的事情，所以
again I'm just borrowing from that same
再一次，我只是从那个借来的
example that we saw last time with the
我们上次看到的例子
spring integration I'm going to adopt
我要采用的春季整合
this API to produce a new message down
该API产生新消息
to the client whenever there is a new
每当有新的情况下给客户
file now we're gonna use this as an
文件，我们将使用它作为
opportunity to use spring integration
使用Spring集成的机会
right which is a not every active API
对，这不是每个活动的API
but it's a it provides event-driven sort
但是它提供了事件驱动的排序
of adapters that we can then plug into
然后可以插入的适配器
the reactive world here so what we're
反应性世界在这里，我们
gonna do is when define a channel on
要做的是在
which we expect new messages to wrap
我们希望新邮件能够包装
read so fun incoming files channel
阅读有趣的传入文件频道
equals published subscribe channel and
等于已发布的订阅频道，并且
well then define well rewrite this code
然后定义好重写此代码
a little bit to to take advantage of
一点点利用
that new channel but now we'll talk
该新频道，但现在我们要谈
about how did it goes into that channel
关于它如何进入该渠道的
in a second we're going to set up a an
一秒钟后，我们将建立一个
inbound adapter a file inbound adapter
入站适配器文件入站适配器
using the spring integration inbound
使用spring集成入站
adapter and equivalent support in the
适配器和同等支持
spring integration file module right we
Spring集成文件模块对我们
can do that but for now
可以做到，但是现在
let's focus on running this code so that
让我们集中精力运行这段代码，以便
we create a handler that gets added to
我们创建一个添加到的处理程序
that channel when we create a new flux
当我们创建新的通量时该通道
for a given session I'm gonna create a
对于给定的会话，我将创建一个
new publisher for a given session so
给定会话的新发布者，因此
let's rewrite this code a bit here we're
让我们在这里重写一下这段代码
gonna get rid of all this and get rid of
要摆脱所有这一切，摆脱
that we're not gonna be calling generate
我们不会打电话给generate
anymore we're not synthesizing data
我们不再合成数据
based on the consumer we're gonna create
根据我们要创造的消费者
a single publisher and we'll give this a
一个发布商，我们将为此
a opportunity to specify what happens
有机会指定发生什么情况
here we can give her a call back here an
在这里，我们可以给她回电
opportunity to a specify what to do and
有机会指定要做什么，以及
we'll send that Pub wouldn't send this
我们将发送该Pub将不会发送此邮件
in send the data in to the publisher
将数据发送到发布者
just as before right so in this case
就像之前一样，在这种情况下
we're gonna do a little bit more work
我们将做更多的工作
but it's it's gonna be done elsewhere
但这将在其他地方完成
right so we're gonna say that we want to
对，所以我们要说我们想
actually send a WebSocket message okay
实际发送一个WebSocket消息好吗
and in order to do this work we're going
为了完成这项工作，我们要
to say first register the connection to
先说注册连接到
the client and then second we want to
客户，然后我们想
connect to the client right so we have
正确连接到客户，所以我们有
two things we need to do in this bit of
这一点我们需要做两件事
code and I think the best way to do that
代码，我认为做到这一点的最佳方法
would be to keep a map of session IDs
将保留会话ID的映射
two handlers that we want to then attach
我们要附加的两个处理程序
to our channel that get written to
写入我们的频道
whenever a message arrives from this
每当有消息从这里到达
particular for this particular WebSocket
特定于此特定的WebSocket
right so I'm gonna say you know
对，所以我要说你知道
connections it's going to be equal to
连接将等于
concurrent hash map of type string whose
字符串类型的并发哈希图，其字符串
payloads are of type message handler
有效载荷是消息处理程序类型
that's the spring messaging message
那是春天的消息
handler component right so we're gonna
处理程序组件正确，所以我们要
create a custom message header type that
创建一个自定义消息头类型
will then keep in that that list there
然后将保留在该列表中
so we're gonna say class forwarding
所以我们要说课程转发
message handler
消息处理程序
which is going to override the it's
这将覆盖它的
going to use rather the WebSocket
将使用而不是WebSocket
session and it'll use the sync WebSocket
会话，它将使用同步WebSocket
flux sync of type WebSocket message and
WebSocket消息类型的流量同步和
it's going to extend the message header
它会扩展消息头
interface of course so we'll have to
界面，所以我们必须
satisfy the contract which we can do
履行我们可以做的合同
fairly straightforwardly so there we go
很简单，所以我们去了
so we have our custom class there and we
所以我们在那里有我们的自定义类
know we're gonna store the session ID so
知道我们要存储会话ID，所以
says an ID equals session that ID and we
说一个ID等于该ID的会话，我们
know that we're gonna need a object
知道我们需要一个物体
member so Val Oh M equals object member
所以Val Oh M等于对象成员
actually we can just use the one in
其实我们可以只用一个
scope that'll be fine and so let's now
范围会很好，所以现在让我们
write this code we're gonna say when a
写这段代码，我们要说的是
message comes in when we're creating a
当我们创建一个
new publisher we're not generating new
新的发布者，我们不会产生新的
values over and over whatever we do in
超越我们所做的一切的价值观
here is there is basically a constructor
这里基本上有一个构造函数
to factory method for a publisher in
工厂中的发布商的工厂方法
this case we're gonna generate a new
在这种情况下，我们将产生一个新的
value in the publisher by producing a
通过产生一个
new value onto the sync by calling same
通过调用相同的值将新值同步
time next whenever in file arrives on
每当文件到达时的下一个时间
the inbound channel so we need to use
入站通道，所以我们需要使用
our pointer to this session and to the
我们指向本次会议以及
sync in this message handler to publish
在此消息处理程序中同步以发布
a message so you know we're gonna do
一条消息，以便您知道我们将要做
that in a second here we're gonna say
一秒钟之后，我们要说
you know message and we'll dereference
您知道消息，我们将取消引用
to the payload payload equals message
到有效载荷等于消息
payload as file right because we know
有效负载作为文件权利，因为我们知道
it's gonna be a Java and IO a Java IO
这将是Java和IO成为Java IO
file so we'll use that and then we're
文件，所以我们将使用它，然后
going to get the the we've got a file
将得到我们有一个文件
event so Fe equals file event and the
因此，Fe等于文件事件，而
session ID will of course be the session
会话ID当然是会话
ID that we've recorded earlier and the
我们之前记录的ID和
path
路径
we'll be the payload absolute path okay
我们将成为有效载荷绝对路径
so there's this there we are and then we
所以我们在那里，然后我们
turn that into a string of course just
把它变成一串当然
as we did before so we'll say Val string
正如我们之前所做的，我们将说Val字符串
equals om dot right value as string f e
等于om点右值作为字符串fe
and then we'll turn that into a text
然后我们将其转换为文本
message TM session dot text message
消息TM会话点文本消息
passing in this string and then finally
传递这个字符串，然后最后
we'll send that using the sync as we did
我们将像以前一样使用同步发送
before so TM passing that in right so
在此之前，TM正确地传递了
same kind of processing code except now
相同的处理代码，除了现在
it's being done at the end of a spring
在春季末完成
integration flow right so that's now why
整合流程正确，这就是为什么
are that connection up we're going to
是连接，我们要
say that whenever a new message whenever
说，每当有新消息
we create this new flux for a new
我们为新的
session for a new connection from the
会话以从
client we're going to create a we're
客户，我们要创建一个
going to map it by its key by its ID in
将通过其键通过其ID映射它
here and we're gonna use a forwarding
在这里，我们将使用转发
message handler passing in the session
会话中传递的消息处理程序
and the sync and then once we've done
和同步，然后一旦完成
that we're going to use the channel
我们将要使用该频道
right I create that we're gonna
对，我创造出我们要
dereference the channel that we've we've
取消引用我们拥有的渠道
got configured up there so we'll say
在那里配置好了，所以我们说
incoming files channel dot subscribe
传入文件通道点订阅
passing in of course the connections
当然通过连接
session that ID keyed message has been
ID密钥消息已通过的会话
now on the other side once this
现在在另一边
publisher is gone we need to clean up
发布者不见了，我们需要清理
that connection right we don't want too
我们也不想这样的连接
many connections and subscribers on that
许多连接和订户
channel for no reason it'll be a memory
通道无缘无故会成为记忆
leak otherwise so in this case we want
否则泄漏，所以在这种情况下，我们要
to clean up that that extra resource and
清理那些多余的资源
the ideal time to do that of course is
当然，理想的时间是
when they client disconnects which we
当他们的客户断开连接时，我们
can get to by overriding the do finally
可以通过覆盖最终做到的事情来解决
method here so here I'm gonna say
方法在这里，所以我要说
incoming file channels unsubscribe and
传入文件通道退订，
we're going to look up the you know the
我们将查找您知道的
message handler in the map as well and
地图中的消息处理程序以及
then of course having done that we can
然后当然可以做到了
say connections that remove
说删除的连接
you know session that ID something now
您知道会话ID现在有问题
we can remove it from the map after
我们可以在之后将其从地图上删除
we've unsubscribed it right we want to
我们已经取消订阅了，我们想要
make sure there's no in-flight
确保没有机上
transactions first so there we go we've
交易第一，所以我们去了
got now this we've written a little bit
现在，我们已经写了一点
of code and of course I'm just running a
代码，当然我只是在运行
publisher here to to send data back it
发布者在这里发送数据回去
should be noticed that no you know
应该注意到，不知道
mention that you can read it it's just
提及您可以阅读它只是
to publish it's a flux so it's a
发布它是一个通量，所以它是一个
publisher of incoming WebSocket messages
传入WebSocket消息的发布者
but that's you know that's a client
但那是你知道那是一个客户
initiated transaction we're not so much
发起的交易我们不是很多
interested in that as we are a server or
对我们感兴趣，因为我们是服务器或
service initiated transaction right so
服务启动交易权，所以
here we go here's our basic arrangement
这里我们去这是我们的基本安排
we have a message handler that's going
我们有一个消息处理程序
to be created each time there's a new
每次有新的时候都要创建
WebSocket request or WebSocket session
WebSocket请求或WebSocket会话
initiated when the WebSocket session is
在WebSocket会话启动时启动
initiated we create a publisher which
首先，我们创建了一个发布商
will be defined as the thing that
将被定义为
produces a new value whenever there is
只要有，就会产生一个新值
an event and then of course the event
一个事件，然后当然是事件
has to come from somewhere somewhere
必须来自某个地方
it'll go through the incoming channel
它会通过传入渠道
but we still need the integration flow
但是我们仍然需要整合流程
to make it happen so let's wire that up
为了实现它，所以让我们联系起来
now as well so we're gonna say incoming
现在也是，所以我们要说传入
incoming file flow integration flow
传入文件流集成流
equals integration flows type from and
等于来自和的积分流类型
we're gonna use the files in bed adapter
我们将使用床适配器中的文件
and here we need to provide a file
在这里我们需要提供一个文件
pointer I don't actually need this in
指针，我实际上并不需要
this case do I so I can use the value
在这种情况下，我可以使用该值
annotation to you know use spell or
您知道的注释使用拼写或
property placeholder resolution or
财产占位符解析或
something like this so I'm gonna use
这样的东西，所以我要用
home desktop in but of course this is
家用台式机，但这当然是
Scotland and Kotlin has its own property
苏格兰和科特林拥有自己的财产
placeholder resolutions in text it looks
它看起来像文本中的占位符分辨率
exactly the same as Springs so we have
与斯普林斯完全一样，所以我们有
to make sure that the language doesn't
确保该语言不
attempt to resolve these variables or
尝试解决这些变量或
these expressions because this is not
这些表达式，因为这不是
you know it's not going to be in the
你知道它不会在
Java like in the in the cotton language
棉花语言中的Java
it's gonna be in the spring spring
春天会在春天
application context that these values
应用程序上下文中这些值
reside so we escape it using that
居住，所以我们使用它逃脱它
backslash there so we're saying is
反斜杠在那里，所以我们说的是
create a in bed adapter looking at the
创建一个躺在床上的适配器
directory there create the directory if
目录在那里创建目录，如果
it doesn't exist and then we want to
它不存在，然后我们想
create a polar so I'm gonna say create a
创建一个极地，所以我要说创建一个
polar of type with the following
具有以下类型的极坐标
metadata right until p.m. dot
元数据直到pm点
p m dot fixed-rate and then use that
pm点固定汇率，然后使用
rate then whenever a message arrives
然后在消息到达时进行评分
we're gonna send it on the incoming
我们将在收到的邮件上发送它
files channel and then we'll get the
文件频道，然后我们将获得
whole built flow and then store it there
整个构建的流程，然后将其存储在那里
and so there we go there's our
所以我们去那里是我们的
integration flow and our embedded depth
整合流程和我们的嵌入深度
there and the polar that will respond to
那里和极地将作出回应
the messages coming in off the adapter
适配器发出的消息
and so on okay so that says look at the
等等，这样就可以看一下
current direction look at the directory
当前方向看目录
specified here which we'll call file
在这里指定，我们将其称为文件
home desktop in create the directory if
家用台式机在创建目录中是否
it doesn't exist and you should scan the
它不存在，您应该扫描
directory every one second or every 1000
每隔一秒钟或每1000个目录
milliseconds for any new data if there
任何新数据的毫秒数（如果有）
is any new files that are there that
是否有任何新文件
weren't there before send a Spring
送春天之前没来
Framework message on the incoming files
传入文件上的框架消息
channel and then something on the other
渠道，然后另一件事
end will listen to it well of course we
最终我们会听得很好
have here a set up that creates a new
这里有一个创建新的设置
subscriber to listen on that channel
订户在该频道上收听
anytime there's a new web socket session
每当有新的Web套接字会话时
so basically we're dynamically adding
所以基本上我们是在动态添加
and removing subscribers based on the
并根据
initiation or termination of a WebSocket
WebSocket的启动或终止
session so let's restart
会话，所以让我们重新启动
now we go to the browser refresh and we
现在我们去浏览器刷新，我们
have to go to the command line here CD
必须去命令行CD
desktop in touch 1 2 3 etc so that's one
触摸桌面1 2 3等，这是一个
client go to another touch 4 if you can
客户如果可以的话，再去碰4
see here both the old browser and the
在这里看到旧的浏览器和
new browser see the new file but they
新的浏览器会看到新文件，但他们
have different sessions right so we've
有不同的会议，所以我们
now got 2 subscribers listening for the
现在有2位订阅者正在收听
records and you can see that reflected
记录，您可以看到反映
here as well right it says incoming
这里也说收到
files channel has 2 subscribers now
文件频道现在有2个订阅者
let's kill this this incognito session
让我们杀死这个隐身会话
and you'll see that incoming file
然后您会看到该传入文件
channels has now one subscriber that's
频道现在有一个订阅者
the one that was yeah the one that's
是的那个是那个
still active so it cleans itself and
仍然活跃，所以它会自我清洁，
take care of itself so here we've looked
好好照顾自己，所以我们在这里
at how to use the reactive API to build
如何使用反应式API进行构建
a WebSocket application you'll see that
一个WebSocket应用程序，您将看到
cognitively it's it's I still find this
认知上是我仍然找到这个
much more approachable to be honest with
说实话，平易近人
you then the spring framework approach
然后是Spring框架方法
the spring framework for approach to to
春天的方法框架
working with WebSockets the spring
在春季使用WebSockets
framework for approach worked just fine
方法框架工作得很好
and it was based on the concepts of
它基于
messaging in the spring framework right
Spring框架中的消息传递权利
so they sent messaging template and all
所以他们发送了消息传递模板和所有
this indeed that work was allowed is
确实允许工作是
what allowed us to extract the spring
是什么让我们提取了春天
integration message and spring
整合信息和春天
integration channel type from spring
弹簧整合型
integration and put it in spring
整合并在春季投入使用
framework it's the basis of that
框架是它的基础
movement and so I'm very glad for all
运动，所以我为所有人感到高兴
that work but I just find it so natural
这项工作，但我觉得它很自然
to think about eventual things you know
考虑一下你知道的最终事情
things of streams of data that may or
可能或
may not occur as publishers interactive
与发布者互动可能不会发生
streams publishers so you know lots of
流发布者，所以您知道很多
good stuff there
那里的好东西
well alright with that thanks very much
很好，非常感谢
for watching and see you next time
下次再见
you
您